Berdugo, how are you, my dear?
I'm all set for my trip.
And the sample?
Ready.
You won't be disappointed.
Well, I'll see you soon,
my dear.
So your theory is that Berdugo
will replace Godfather
as the supplier here in Valmora.
Seems like it,
that's why I came to you.
Why did you even need
to come here to Valmora?
To accompany Joey?
You're such a good friend.
And a dedicated Journalist.
Just remember, posture, calm,
eye contact.
She will notice the difference.
Do you need all this
just to get her attention?
You're a good guy, Peter.
You will be good for Joey.
Last one!
You can stay here as long
as you need.
Thanks, Zoey.
No problem.
Andrew, can I talk to you
just for a moment?
Joey is pretty.
Maybe you're doing this to...
to help my friend.
Joey, my child...
Father, I'm right.
You're the guy I was following
earlier.
How did that happen?
Didn't your car burn down?
Long story, my child.
Bro, I'll go ahead.
Are you leaving now?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
that I moved.
Where?
Somewhere closer to where
Theresa might be.
Don't worry.
I'm being very careful.
Sorry, my child,
but this is the only way I can
be sure you're safe.
I'll bring down the syndicate.
No one can know I'm alive.
Not even Andrew?
Joey, who are you talking to?
Mother.
She's not here.
I haven't seen Joey yet.
And she didn't tell me
she was coming here.
But okay, I'll let you know
when she suddenly arrives.
What happened to your face
of the night look?
Nothing, I just thought of Joey.
She didn't even tell me
she was coming home.
Why would she tell you?
Are you her boyfriend
to inform you?
- What?
- Joke!
Just a joke.
You're getting angry again.
You're overly serious.
You know the situation
with our friend, right?
She lost someone.
I'm not sulking, okay?
I was just worried about her.
I want to comfort her, but how?
I don't know where she is.
She didn't say if she was coming
here or not.
Here.
There are only two rooms
in the house, which means...
Which means I'll sleep here in
the living room, on the sofa.
Okay.
The bed is ready in that room.
You can sleep there tonight.
Thanks, Zoey.
I'm going to rest, okay?
I'm tired.
Good night, Joey.
You're so obvious.
Obvious?
What do you mean?
It's obvious to you
that you like Joey.
I'm just concerned
about my friend.
Really?
Because I remember you used
to look at me that way.
When we were still together.
I remember that look.
I know that look.
Good night, Andrew.
The number you dialed
is unattended.
Please try your call...
You want some jam, Mom?
No. No, thank you, my child.
Hon, good morning.
Let's have breakfast.
No. I'll take care of something.
Good morning, Mom.
Good morning.
It seems like you have
an early appointment.
Time is money, Hon.
I need to prepare for my
business meeting in a few days.
Which reminds me,
I won't be home
for the next few days.
It looks like your appointment
is important.
Do you want me to come lwith
you?
No need, Hon.
You'll just get bored.
Anyway, we'll just celebrate
when I come home.
Wow, this looks like big time,
Hon.
Okay.
I know you'll be successful
no matter what you do.
Of course, you know me.
I always get what I want.
Mom!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'll just go back to my room.
Help her.
No, I can do it.
I told you not to help me!
Don't you understand!
Mom, she was just trying
to help you!
Has she taken her meds?
She looks like she's having
a meltdown.
Mom's moods are changing again.
Maybe she needs a change
of meds.
Are you okay?
It's my Mommy.
My sister said she is having
mood swings again.
Just go home.
Be with your Mother.
Tell her you talked to me
and I'm alive.
Maybe you need to go home?
It's okay if they're looking
for you.
I'll go with you and come home.
No, it's okay.
My sister's there.
I'll just ask for updates.
Let's continue this.
Zoey?
Are you sure about the one we're
waiting for?
Yes.
He's been my asset
for a long time.
He's here.
Who are you with?
My friends.
These guys are okay.
What's the news
about drugs here?
Customers are coming
from everywhere.
The drugs have been running out
since Godfather disappeared.
That's why there's
no one supplying.
Hasn't a new supplier come in?
Maybe you've heard a new name,
it's Berdugo.
Berdugo?
This is the first time
I heard that name.
Excuse me.
Hello, Mom?
My child, Joey...
Are you back in your dorm?
You didn't inform me.
Sorry, Mother.
I was really tired and fell
asleep last night.
That's why you and Peter
haven't seen each other, right?
Peter?
Yes, we haven't talked.
Joey, I'm going to the precinct
to get an update about your dad.
I hope they release the remains
of Miguel.
Mother, if it's about Father,
you don't need to worry.
We don't have any problems
with that anymore.
What?
Why did you say we don't have
any problems
with your father anymore?
Father, I'll help you.
It's hard if you're alone.
You'll find Berdugo easier
if you have someone with you.
Father, I just don't want
anything bad to happen to you.
My child, don't.
Just go home.
Be with your Mother.
I mean, don't worry because
you might get sick, Mother.
Joey, answer my question first.
Why did you say we won't have
any more problems
with your Father?
Because Father doesn't want us
to think about him.
He wants us to just get on
with our lives.
That's why I'll do it,
even though it hurts me
that Father is gone,
I'll just take care
of the things I need to do
here in the dorm.
Go ahead and finish everything
so you can come home soon.
Love you, Joey.
I love you, Mom.
Sorry, Father,
if I don't obey you.
I know you need my help
more now.
I want to know who
that Berdugo is.
Just as soon as you get
any information about him,
let me know right away.
Okay, Ma'am.
All right,
I'll take care of that.
All right.
Mister, as soon as you
have any information,
let me know, okay?
I'll give you a free snack.
Promise me that, Ma'am, okay?
Promise.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Sir...
Hey, it seems like you're doing
something stupid again.
Sir, you're being suspicious
again.
Someone is just asking
for some help.
They're asking if I know
anything about Berdugo.
Do you know him, Sir?
No. I don't know Berdugo.
Hey, you, get out of my sight.
I might arrest you. Get out!
Yes, Sir.
Hello? Why are you calling?
Is there a problem?
Sir, someone is asking about
Berdugo.
That's our boss's name,
right, Sir?
Find out who's looking
for Berdugo.
Okay, Sir, I'll take care of it.
I'll find out.
Hello, Peter?
Joey!
It's good I finally talked
to you. Where are you?
Your Mother is looking for you.
She's worried about you.
I talked to Mother already.
Okay, don't worry.
But where are you now?
Andrew and I are following
a lead.
We're here in Valmora.
Someone is helping us,
so we're okay here, we're safe.
I'll just call you
when we get back to Manila.
Sorry, we're just busy here.
Here.
Maybe you haven't had
your coffee yet.
We left early.
Thank you.
Delicious.
Of course.
I still remember how you like
your coffee.
I remember a lot of things,
you know.
Are you still angry about
what happened to us before?
No, where did you suddenly pull
that out?
Andrew, it's been a while.
Let's not talk about it.
You know, just enjoy your coffee
because I'm the only one
who can do that.
I hope your informant
gets some news.
Because at this point,
I feel like we're on a dead end.
Unless you have something
to share.
There's this woman
under my radar,
it's Delilah.
She's the one I'm working on
right now.
She's my current target
because she's the one suspected
of being in charge of drug
distribution here in Valmora.
You know, if Berdugo is meeting
someone here, it might be her.
That's good.
You know, I'm having a hard time
catching Delilah.
because I don't have any
evidence against her yet.
So my plan is to get close
to her.
She has a lot of businesses here
in Valmora.
One of them is the new
Nature Hotel and Resort.
What I heard is that she's
staying there now.
Okay, I'll check in there
to investigate.
Andrew, don't.
It's my job to go undercover,
so I should be the one
to do that.
Zoey, we can do this together.
- I'll help you.
- That's even worse!
Your face is too recognizable,
Andrew.
And if they see you
at the resort,
the people there might be
alerted.
You know, I'll just come back
here to update you.
If I get any information
about Berdugo, okay?
Andrew.
I know you, okay?
But please, just do what I say?
Just stay put.
I'll take care of it.
I'm leaving.
Mom, take your medicine first,
okay?
Why did you bring that?
Where's the caregiver?
She left already, Mom.
Sorry, I couldn't stop her.
Because she was shocked
by what you did, Mom.
She's very sensitive.
She should just leave.
She didn't do anything wrong.
Mom, how many caregivers have
left here because of you?
Is there a problem, Mom?
Maybe you want to talk about it.
Just tell me.
How can I help you if you
don't tell me the problem?
Andrew...
I heard your conversation
with Zoey.
So what now?
Is it really a dead end for us?
When did that even stop us
from making a plan?
Has "Joey On Duty" lost her
courage?
What if Delilah is really
the one Berdugo came here for?
And if we're able to confirm
that theory,
then we can set him up,
and we can expose him.
And we can bring justice
to everything he did
to my family.
Yes,
and if your father is alive
and if he needs help when he's
facing Berdugo, we'll be there.
Okay, I'm game.
But what are we going to do?
Actually, I've already thought
of something.
But, I don't know if you'll
agree.
I hope you will.
Why? What is that?
Everything is ready for
your guest's arrival,
Madam Delilah.
Are you sure, Francis?
Yes, Madam.
I even had a meeting with
the resort staff
to make sure they would give
the guest VIP treatment.
It should be.
I don't want to be embarrassed.
If this deal goes South,
I will lose a lot,
and you will lose too.
Madam, that won't happen.
Hi.
I would like to get a room,
please.
Okay, Ma'am.
Are you with someone?
I wish, but I'm alone.
You need to tighten security
here at the hotel.
I don't want to put my deal
with Berdugo at risk.
Yes, Madam.
I already assigned someone.
Good.
Boss Delilah,
I'm sorry if I burned the money
from what was sold.
I got carried away.
I'll just pay you right away.
You know I don't like being
fooled.
What will happen to my business
if my people keep outsmarting
me?
Give me another chance.
I'll give you your money back
right away!
I'll find a way!
You should have done
that a long time ago.
- I'm sorry.
- Boss...
Because if one does it,
everyone will do it.
Boss...
Boss, have mercy on me, Boss!
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- Wow, it's beautiful here!
- Of course. Yes?
- Wait. Let's take a picture.
Okay, okay.
Something's going through
my daughter's mind.
Chief, she has a feeling
that Miguel is still alive.
I'm begging you.
Just a little more patience.
Thank you, Chief.
I might not be able to take care
of my foundation anymore.
Mom lost her caregiver.
Ma'am, if you can't find anyone,
I can.
That guy in red,
he called Delilah his boss.
I feel like we can get better
results if we work together,
Zoey.
Boss, they seem to be getting
suspicious.
So that there won't be any
problems,
I'll meet with Delilah.
Hello there!
I didn't know I had a neighbor.
I'm Madam Delilah.
I'm Joey.